A Guide to the University of Virginia, Student Council, Reports and Surveys, 1966-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia, Student Council, Reports and Surveys 1966-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/2/2.892
This collection consists of 270 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1989 July 19.
Scope and Content Information
Includes reports and surveys on student activities fees, first year writing program (ENWR), Birdwood, day care, housing, Charlottesville Info, Emergency Services, Handicapped, National On Campus Report, Rotunda Committee, Cavalier Daily, Social Programs--Funding, Summer Stipend, Youth Center Reports, Student Activity Fee (Comparisons with Other States).
Contents List
- Alternatives to Birdwood-Letter to Mr. Catlin 1978-1979 (Box 1)
- Alternatives to Birdwood-A Report by Task Force to Student Council 1979 Feb (Box 1)
- Birdwood-Administrative Division Reports 1978 (Box 1)
- Birdwood-Development Plan 1973 (Box 1)
- Birdwood Report/Correspondence [1979-1980] (Box 1)
- The Birdwood Report-A Residential College Plan 1978-1979 (Box 1)
- Birdwood Reports-Miscellaneous [1966-1979], 2 folders (Box 1)
- Birdwood Poll n.d. (Box 1)
- Birdwood-The Six In-House Documents 1968-1974 (Box 1)
- Birdwood Student Poll 1978-1980 (Box 1)
- Catlin Report-Review of Housing Sites 1979 (Box 1)
- Cavalier Daily 1975-1978 (Box 1)
- Charlottesville Info 1978 (Box 2)
- Committee Reports [1976-1978] (Box 2)
- Comprehensive Plan 1979 (Box 2)
- Council Officer's Report and Constitution [1976-1978] (Box 2)
- Development Plan-Final Report 1973 Mar (Box 2)
- A Dream Deferred [1967-1970] (Box 2)
- Emergency Services 1979 (Box 2)
- Employment and Job Discrimination 1975 (Box 2)
- ENWR 1-A Survey 2 volumes [1972], 3 folders (Box 2)
- Expansion Report 1971 (Box 2)
- Handicapped 1978 (Box 2)
- Housing 1974-1978 (Box 2)
- Housing/Family Studies 1981 (Box 3)
- Landlord-Tenant Act 1974 (Box 3)
- National On Campus Report [1975-1976] (Box 3)
- Plavrick Report 1980 Feb 19 (Box 3)
- Report of the Student Council Appropriations Process Study Committee 1983 Apr 27 (Box 3)
- Rotunda Committee 1975 (Box 3)
- Social Programs-Funding 1979-1982 (Box 3)
- Student Activity Fee - Bob Baxter's Study [1973] (Box 3)
- Student Activity Fee - Comparisons with Other States [1975-1976], 1-2 of 3 folders (Box 3)
- Student Activity Fee - Comparisons with Other States [1975-1976], 3 of 3 folders (Box 4)
- Student Activity Fee - Bert Ellis' Study 1975 Apr 18 (Box 4)
- Student Activity Fee Study - House Bill #547 [1976-1977], 2 folders (Box 4)
- Student Activity Fee - Va Colleges [1972-1976] (Box 4)
- Summer Stipend 1977-1978 (Box 4)
- University of Louisville [1979-1981] (Box 4)
- The West Virginia University Campaign - Threshold to Greatness [1978-1983] (Box 4)
- Youth Center Reports [1981] (Box 4)